Jhaal
that this quarter inch taught us this, a health
suit, how many carats is gold,
15, okay or after that a very beautiful, a
best friend comes in front of you when you are in
that light, friends, a healthy sun,
you should take a helping of how much thought, why not do it because you will need that mark, if you have a plate, then this constipation which is there, this health can be cured, it will not break it, as I did a video call, so you
fans, you people have liked this video
very much, if you have
not seen this video, then you can watch this video by clicking on the i button,
or you
can watch this video by writing in the description box and clicking on the link, 200 common
people,
my maximum efforts to make a maximum, only to
call and press, so
I thought for that, please
make a video in detail, so through this video
I will tell you stop 20 friends, top ten
in Begusarai, the limit on other routes, it is
difficult to cover growth in one video, so I thought of making a series of five videos i.e.
part one and part two part three
lakh  For rent of your body or two
classes in this video and different as per
your requirement like maternity opt
top in this way all the points will be there in the plan
and there will be vest plans friends in today's
video in this video I am going to tell you about two
plans with unique features which no other prayer will get
in class from such teacher
so this video is very important do
not skip the video watch if you are
thinking of taking health tips or you
already have a health insurance policy
you are not satisfied with the plans
features are not subscribed on the plan
or you are not getting cancer from the company
then you can support that plan you want to
take that plan or want to fold that you
can contact us on our whatsapp number friends if you are an
urgent or you are an insurance advisor
you wanted to make your career in health this year
want to take their fans you
can contact us on whatsapp
you will get complete guidance and support from us to
grow your business
if you have not subscribed to our channel yet then do it it
is free  We will
not allow sufficient because such interesting
videos and knowledge zone videos like mutual
fund LIC and other function related to
provide, you will get all these videos through this channel,
I upload videos in my hand and
after subscribing, you
must press the notification button so that you keep
getting notifications, so friends it does
not take much time, let me start,
hello friends Marshall is ill
and you will see, let's start with
Ajay,
friends the first plan that I am going to
discuss is the only M
Secure HDFC Agro company has its own
monthly plan in which there is a special benefit,
secure benefit
that if you take Aslam's medicine, then
within 10 minutes
it will double, this tenth class will get
constipation of tenth, then Tilak will get less pressure, the
second benefit from the intake is that the
product should be made, another
example is like if a claim comes and
asks for 1 lakh in the previous My Lucky, whatever
water is there on tent decoration is extra,
like non-medical expenses, this is fit  It is done, so the
Congress has done this item in Assam and Manipur, so in this one
like it is said that in the house of a couple, one has to
pay up to 40% of the oil, the
time of giving, but in this policy overcome, but in
Indore medical expenses of B will be covered,
with Protect Brigade,
in a very strong plant, there is another great benefit which is
Plus Benefits, if you have taken a claim
in the policy or not, your 7th minute
60% will increase, plus next year
if I have taken Tailor's Police, then the
Plus Benefit will increase or the
next 50% of the reply will increase and plus will be
Tailor's Police and your Plus
Benefits will go, this is don't like, plus
your Secure Benefit which I have
told is equal to zero, this
is retail and is on your head, if you add then
after 2 years it simply happens to you, that
Third Tilak gets imposed, if Delhi Police has
taken the policy, then the Third Tilak gets possession, so
after that  This is a very good
feature in this plan which is
not available in other classes.
Snake benefit is in Islam, that is restore
benefit, that is, suppose for example
you have taken a policy of 10 lakhs, the first one who
killed him agreed to Amla and both the
latitudes are saved and the next plan which has
asked for permission, five people have been
shot, then you will get 45 lakhs
in this case, there is a restore facility,
as if the next film comes, it will be hundred
percent, if it gets 10 lakhs then
instead of capsicum, you will get 2 lakhs from the facility of Kabzi Samish, that is, if
we have any
questions then there are news in this plan, the next one will be given
before getting admitted in this 1628 hospital,
in this case there is Congress,
so there is
5 lakh 10 lakh 06
and you can take the smallest of 2 crores, if we
talk about entry in this case, then friends, if it is not
completed then you can
enter and
this is the
maximum
Subscribe to and for this if you have a
claim from the company then
subscribe
so you
can take this on the side that if you do it for more than one lakh then
you
can take any one so there is a
teleporter in this episode of A Profiler so when will you get Dhairya kind
and in individual ₹15 for every checkup
back 10 lakh understand ₹5000 will
get 2000 in family quarters there are divisional
commissioners from time to time except for 15 lakhs
then you will get Rs.8000 in family floater
and individual will get ₹4000 health
checkup in 2025 and it is found out that Aamir is
infected then you will get ₹10 in family floater and ₹5000 in
individual
in front of 12 crore you will get 15000
in Yagna and ₹1000 for individual if we
talk about Islam then
Meghwar is no cosmetic surgery will be covered
any
subscribe it is the
company that the rest of the normal candid
expression is  3810 any plan gets
coverage from countries this is long
but zoological diseases are standard
explanation 130 means if you have taken your policy today then
third after that normal digestive
diseases will start appearing and
zone pacific any surgery and price hernia
attract stone and those who want problem in the fort then
subscribe and
subscribe like anyone can
decide if they feel then
subscribe
detailed information if there is something else then you can
comment in the comment box you can
contact through WhatsApp
friends there is another feature that we
absolutely need so we will make in the video do
not skip the video next plan friends it
is Max Bupa first match was a company right now
lemon first is in the name of this company the
name of that loan is rear showroom given and
what is the transfer condition in the plan from teacher to class we will
add ML at
this time this is the feature which is
different from all the other plans it is a pitch of Islam
and unique features in the year in which there is
unlimited restore facility
like I did  There is definitely a comment in the description box
about 10 lakh
rupees, but here the 10 lakh structure
will be Chris statement of this, this is that multiple
times Bristol 65 that you can lie in Islam,
so this is the plus point
in this plan, the second benefit which is soaked in benefits, that is,
NCP, you can say no claim
bonus is not plan, then only duty no
claim bonus will be given, you must have seen it,
then addiction in this also the Muslim bonus is
on leave, sensitive version two has increased,
hundred percent claim can also be added in Islam, so
friends, Islam, which you like, room
rent, no matter which MS Word you use, there is no
limit on this,
you can use it, so
345678910100
576 and if you have not subscribed till the maximum, then if you
subscribe on this side, then it does positive before getting admitted in soon
and 2 minute verification is available to you in Islam,
but Orient Express
also gives you literate coverage of Islamic  If it is
available then we have the benefit of these,
work phase means in Hindi
we have a corrupt person, it is a combination of 10 minutes, so the
maximum city
benefit that you can avail is ₹5000 and
in family doctor the maximum hair benefit that happens in
life, then the maximum limit in this
plan is ₹10 checkup, you can wear a bichua,
friends,
another benefit in Nigam Health Insurance Company is life
health benefits, in which you can get a discount of up to
30 percent by downloading the app of minimum balance,
for this if you
need detailed information then you can go to the comment box and
comment,
you can contact us through WhatsApp, friends,
after this, so Bill Scrabble is cash
celebs
caught off-guard
Robert Magar, then this batsman will earn 2.5 lakh
maximum Adams news, entry in 2 crore club in Islamic double role, entry entry is of
108 different styles, that is
3023 ghee  You can subscribe to 6 maximum entries. The
first option
also placed
Shekhar benefits means that
like
in the
front
knowledge question of blouse, there will be
cosmetic surgery in it, there will be
no button express news coverage, any
like support investigation and evolution,
even if the cross line is reduced, the
company does not cover it, there is bomb expression in it, the
rest are
expressions from some specific playlist, this is
normal Kumari, that too is pimple coverage,
as I told in my mental and
normal remedies, it is not like that, any
normal diseases, they get
cured after 30 days, rest of the accidents,
constipation gets cured due to dengue, anyone is
talking about the fair presented in the mediclaim policy,
after that this
vaccine of Congressmen became a problem, cataract, hernia,
store piles, planning from hysterectomy,
which services are basically trees, so
friends, these were the best to
subscribe, how did you like the features, if
you need details on some more points, you
can comment in the comment box,
Next nine, something else also  If you feel
that I should make videos on some other topic, then
I will definitely post that video
for you guys. Friends, if you have
not subscribed yet, then subscribe
so that you will get such informative and
interesting videos on this channel. So,
definitely press the bell icon so that you get the
notification immediately. Friends, if you are
thinking about health, it is ready
because there are health insurance policy
features or if there is a problem in the engine,
everyone is liking the feature of the plan, then
you can complete it by breaking it and
pressing it with new full, then you
can contact me on WhatsApp. Friends, if you are
an urgent cardamom, if you are an insurance
advisor, you
want to make a career in the health insurance industry, then you
can contact us through WhatsApp.
You will get idols through our team, so in the
next video of mine, I have already
told them that
in the conspiracy of ₹90, in this, friends, you will get
lakhs of American plan, do
not just watch it, it is very important in the video,
so do not miss it at all. We will
meet in the next video, till then
bye-bye Jai Hind Jai Bharat friends  Thank you
so much 28 Ajay had reached
Ajay
[Music]
Ajay ko Ajay ko Ajay ko Ajay ko